Sean Gyuris

Junior Web Developer

Im a motivated junior developer with a passion for problem solving and collaborating. My experience in the geosciences has exposed me to a range of challenging and fast-paced work environments. I am dedicated to following my life-long passion for learning and utilise my knowledge and ambition to add value to any team I join.

CONTACT

0420956947

sean_gyuris@hotmail.com

seanlb02.com

https://github.com/seanlb02

Sydney, Australia

LANGUAGES

Bash

HTML5/CSS3

Python

Javascript

SQL

FRAMEWORKS

React

Next JS

Flask

Express

Tailwind (CSS)

SKILLS

Databases

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

GIS

- ArcGIS
- QGIS

Testing

- Pytest
- Jest

Source Control

- Github
- Bitbucket

Agile

Trello

Deployment

- Vercel
 - AWS

KEY PROJECTS

Chattree

- A broadcast messaging app where users can read the DMs and group chats of people they follow
- NextJS, Express, Socket.io [websocket], MongoDB

<u>DayOf</u>

- · Live music events map of Sydney
- NextJS, Express, Leaflet, MongoDB

Serene

- · Mental health logging and remote tracking app
- React, Express, MongoDB

EDUCATION

Coder Academy 2022-2023

Dip. IT (bootcamp) [Distinction]

Charles Sturt University 2022-2023

Masters of GIS & Remote Sensing

Macquarie University 2018--2020

Masters of Science (Geology/Geophysics) [HD]

UNSW 2012-2015

Bachelor of Science (Geology/Geography)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sandfire Resources (ASX:SFR)

Jan 2022 - June 2022

Exploration Geologist

- AC/RC, DD rig supervision, logging
- · Contractor management

Manuka Resources (ASX:MKR)

May 2021 -- Jan 2021

Exploration Geologist

- · AC/RC, DD rig supervision, logging
- · GIS analysis and map publication